The majority of you
are leaving sales on the table by,
first of all, thinking that
a landing page and a website
are the same thing. They're not.
You know by now that I'm not a big fan of
sales calls, and if you want people to do
business with you without having to jump
on a call with them or beg them to do
business, this is the way.
I've been in the Discord this morning,
and rather than
going to the studio,
I'm making this video from the spare room.
This is the one room in the house
that my missus lets me keep messy.
Nutonic Australia flavors down here.
Parcels that I haven't opened yet.
Excuse the chaos. So this here
is a landing page.
It can often look like a website,
but it's a landing page.
And easiest way to distinguish this is,
first of all, there is only one thing for
you to click here, and that
is the Tell Me More button.
There is no About Me, there
is no anything else.
So if I go to apple.com, this
is a website.
And the thing is,
because you've got Store and Mac...
If we just go through here, we've got one,
two, three, four, five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten.
You've got all of these submenus here.
This part here you could call a bit of a
landing page, but it's a website.
You can find out things about whatever.
So on your landing page,
this first area across here we're going to
call above
the fold.
That is the first thing you see
when you land.
You'll notice that I've kept the branding
pretty small.
We've started with here with a very
subtle, this is an appeal to authority.
Now, you don't need one of these.
It's just saying, okay,
if this guy's worked with
7,000 coaches,
he's probably got some kind of legitimacy.
Now,
this heading is what I would call the
promise.
It's the first thing you need to put
there.
And by reading that,
you should know everything you need to
know about what I do
and how I can help you. If this just said,
"Get rich," you don't know who I'm
talking to.
Grow your business with the systems
and strategies I personally used to
generate eight figures in online sales,
which is again, an appeal to authority,
but
a promise of what you're going to get.
We made this bit a little bit harder to
see, the step-by-step how-to guide,
because
it doesn't quite have the importance of
this.
Then the subheading
is where you can give context
and nuance on your promise.
So I would rather this bit up here
was a bit briefer, and this bit here was a
little bit easier to get the
understanding.
Growing your online presence doesn't have
to feel scammy, transactional, or
inauthentic.
I'll show you how to create a brand for
your business online, build an
audience, and create an army of loyal,
paying customers without wasting years
playing trial and error. Again,
I'm pretty much saying
that what you're buying into
is my experiences. Now,
here we have a VSL, video sales letter.
Short.
Should never be anything over three
minutes.
Hello,
and welcome to my business mentorship,
where pretty much I'm going to teach
you three pillars that I think
are really important. Cool.
Now, there are other landing pages
that I've got.
So this is for my short-form content
creation course.
Sell about 20 of these a day.
Again, appeal to authority,
branding pretty minimal. Promise.
Become a master in short-form content
creation.
Everyone's like,
"That's what I want to do.
I want to grow my Instagram," TikTok,
whatever.
Build your personal brand,
reach audiences worldwide, become a pro.
Single greatest return on investment
activity for your business. Again, VSL.
We need a video that's going to represent,
and they can scroll down and get more
information. Now, this
is different to what I call a squeeze
page.
A squeeze page has a different objective.
So at no point on this page am I trying to
get your information.
If we look at this squeeze page where I
give you a template for a high-converting
landing page, and by the way,
I'll put the links for these in the
description so
you can have a look at them.
The only really thing here to click on
is to give me
your email address. And again,
the other thing that's performed really
well for my
business is the 30 days, 30 insights,
and 30 ways to optimize your business.
Again, no VSL needed.
All I'm getting here is data.
And again, these links in the description,
feel free to copy them, steal them, rip
them off, whatever.
So it's very important that
when people land above the fold, we
have a promise, we have a subheading,
and we have a VSL. Pricing also on show.
So if you can't afford it, you're out.
If you can afford it,
you might want to listen more.
A call to action button should be
repeated, but we'll get into it now.
So some people will watch a VSL and buy.
Some people will not watch a VSL,
and they'll need more information.
There are different types of buyers
online, and what we're doing here
is putting
something for everyone.
Some people might just click Tell Me More.
Going to take them down to the bottom bit
here.
And really what we've done for this one
is to say,
learn the three highest leverage
online skills to attract
and convert your ideal clients.
So every person that lands here that's
perfect for me will want to have
landing pages that convert,
write email marketing campaigns that sell,
and they'll
want to make better content.
So they're thinking, "Okay,
this sounds too good to be
true." So for me, this
is another place to put what I would call
this segment
a reason to believe.
So the reason to believe segment can be
testimonials, can be
what people say about you. But
if you're in your infancy of business
and you
haven't really done that much,
this could be a good place to just hammer
home a
money-back guarantee.
Because some of you just don't have the
amount of
testimonials you might need for this
section.
So give people a reason to believe.
Got a testimonial here from Eric.
He's crushing it.
He just bought a Lamborghini Urus. Big up.
Multiple seven-figure businesses,
hundreds of millions of people reached my
content. Eight figures and, again,
appeal to authority.
Now,
appeal to authority for me for this page
is going to be monetary because
that's really the main outcome
that you want.
For you,
this could be results for your fitness
business, maybe your accountancy
firm. If you're an accountancy firm,
you could say about saved £7 million in
tax this year that
was set up through family trusts.
For your personal training business,
could be something different.
And these things here,
it's actually alluding to the status in
which I've
got some recognition for.
Because a lot of you actually think you
want money.
You don't. A lot of you want status,
and that's fine. What you want
is recognition.
What you want is people to perceive you as
being very good at what you do.
Actually, some of you
are very good at what you do.
You just don't get the status
that you deserve for it.
That's what you're after.
And then down here,
we tell people exactly what they get.
Usually, I'm not a big fan of this, oh,
valued at this.
Some people say free e-book valued at
£500.
It's not valued at £500.
But because these courses
are individually sold for these
prices, we can do it. Again,
some more people here,
and then how to buy.
This one, same thing. Show some visuals,
show the courses for.
We're basically trying to give people a
menu. That's what this page is for.
It's a menu. Appeal to authority,
reason to believe.
Short-form content mastery.
So I've picked seven of the most recent
pages, and we're just going to go through
them soon. So I haven't looked at these.
I've got no experience.
I didn't pre-study these like Ed does.
I just jump into them.
Again,
there's going to be a link in the
description if you want to apply for me to
go through this. I'll do that as well.
Okay, first thing, colors.
We have red, green, blue, and that
is a different type of
green. And we have blue ticks.
Straight away, unless you're color blind,
this
doesn't work.
And we've got this beige up here.
You'll notice that my pages are dark mode,
which you've done here, but we stick to
a color palette that's just a little bit
nicer.
If this was just black and white,
it would look nicer.
We've got too many colors here.
So get early access to exclusive discount.
No context.
I don't really understand what that is,
so I'll probably delete that.
That gives us then more room for above the
fold. Stop just watching football.
Start reading it like a coach. This,
I think,
needs to be thought out a bit better.
I actually want to know what I'm going to
get from this.
So, so far, I've read that.
I don't know what it is you sell
or what you do.
Learn the frameworks
and the seven-day system,
completely self-paced, designed to
change how you see the game forever so you
can finally understand why things happen
on the pitch without needing any
qualifications or experience.
I still don't know what it is I'm getting.
So am I supposed to be a football coach?
Am I learning more about football?
Is this as a spectator?
You've watched football your whole life
But have you ever truly understood it?
Because the truth is,
every time you watch a game,
you're probably missing about
80% of what's really going on.
I used to think I got football.
I knew formations, I played weekly.
I even-
That sound effect, bring it down a bit.
If any of you are unsure,
if you've got any whooshes or swirls
or whatever, they're
better off being too quiet than too loud
7-Day Football IQ Accelerator.
So what I'm not getting from this
is the outcome that I get from doing this.
So is it going to make me a better coach?
Is it going to get me into academies?
I want to know the outcome
that we're going to get.
So before,
we spoke quite heavily in some of my
landing pages about what is on the
other side.
Become a master in content creation.
That's the outcome.
So I would like you to do a lot more of
that.
Okay,
we've got some of the information here,
maybe the reason to believe.
The world of football can get confusing.
I still don't really know what this is.
So we want a promise.
This could even be like
become a better football coach subheading.
Watching football games enough isn't
enough to obtain the mastery needed to be
an
elite coach. With this program, outcome.
Here's another one. Okay.
First things first, bit of overwhelm.
Again, I'm a big fan of dark mode.
All this white kind of freaks me out.
Again, you're center aligned up here.
You're center aligned, then this
is left aligned, which kills me.
This could be a brand, cool,
but we've missed the opportunity to
have a heading or to tell me what it is.
Land on this.
Will Nicholls, windsurf
or wing foil coach.
Join waitlist book now.
Join waitlist for what? Book now?
What am I booking?
If you haven't told me at this point,
if this was to say summer retreats, I
would be like, "Oh, yeah,
join the waitlist.
I want to join the summer retreat."
But there's none of that.
Upcoming coaching weeks.
Accelerate your progression expert
world-class
windsurf/foil destinations.
This should be your title probably.
I would delete this because most people
know who you are because to arrive on this
page, they've come from either marketing,
socials, or maybe even a chatbot.
So this needs a bit of a restructure.
The heading.
Also,
I'm not a massive fan of text going on
images, and if that image is going to
be behind there,
we can either add a bit of a stroke to
this, or we can darken the
image in the background.
I don't particularly like the way
this is spread out. I also think
that you could have a
world map with little pins on it so
that I can see which one is nearest me,
and then I could click on Greece
and get the dates.
Okay, so Greece, Egypt, Dutch Caribbean.
Don't know where that is.
So yeah,
there maybe could be something a bit more
creative with that.
But join the waitlist. The thing is,
right, if you want someone's
email address about this, I think this
is a bit all over the place.
You are trying to sell them something,
then telling them to join the waitlist.
Surely couldn't you run some kind of lead
magnet which is about
getting better at one of these things,
get their email address,
then pepper people
on the email address about your upcoming
events?
To me, yeah, that's where I would go.
Will Nicholls.
You should be getting people's email
address by giving them something of value,
and
then once you've got their email address,
you should email that list and go, "Hey,
why don't you come to one of these?"
That's how I would do that.
And again, about Will.
Is anyone coming here cold from SEO?
Doubt it.
And this is not what we want because you
want someone's email address, right?
And if they click on this,
they've gone to your YouTube.
Well, it's not terrible.
But then let's say I watch this video.
What separates the $20,000 a month agency
coaches from-
Oh, I'm sold in.
And then suddenly I'm like, oh,
this looks good
The average new YouTube-
And then I'm watching someone else's
videos, and I'm gone.
So rather than get my email address,
you've now lost me. All right.
Monk House and Company,
the newsletter for founders who refuse to
remain trapped
every Thursday.
This I don't think should pop up.
I would rather have something of value,
and if it is of value, just tell me
straight away what that thing is.
And again, newsletter,
some people call them
snooze letters.
It shouldn't be called a newsletter.
So my "30 Ways,
30 Days," you could call a newsletter.
It's not a newsletter,
but I would never call it that.
I would say,
"30 Ways to Revolutionize Your Business."
So if you were out here
trying to sell a business
that runs without them, this title here.
Or actually, you've got it here.
Build a company that runs without you.
Retire early.
Spend more time with your family.
Stop being in the office every day.
Every week,
I'm going to deliver a strategy you can
use to remove yourself from the
business. Okay,
if we look at this website with the
landing page function here.
About, work with us, resources, contact.
I don't mind because this looks pretty
good. Build a company
that runs without you.
Promise. Love it. Step out the weeds.
Build an elite team
and scale exponentially.
Love it. This is perfect. Very good.
Which future is your business heading
towards? Great. VSL. Book a call.
Usually, I don't like calls,
but maybe for like a consultancy
and coaching,
mentoring business, it could be necessary.
Let's have a little look on this,
shall we? Hmm. Yes.
This is what I was talking about with
the...
I could be interested in chatting to you.
This is one of the reasons I don't like
sales calls is because I'm not going to
get
on a call with you at 4:00 in the morning.
The empty diary effect.
And it looks like you're keeping
that kind of scarce. It's all right.
All these colors are a bit mad.
At least you matched the pinks.
Okay, this is nice. This is very nice.
The one thing I would like
is potentially another option,
I suppose contact.
Yeah, I suppose I can always email you.
I like that.
What I would like to see
is to an A/B split test a dark mode of
this.
White branding, white text,
dark background. But again,
that's just me being me.
Again, I'd probably try this dark mode.
The reason that I love dark mode, right,
is I watch all my YouTube in dark mode,
and I believe the majority of people do.
So, oh, new podcast has gone up.
The problem is-
You guys should probably watch that.
Where were we? Okay, above the fold.
Website.
Definitely website, not landing page.
Pictures. Cool.
Is this your heading?
Looking to achieve your handstand,
calisthenic, and mobility goals?
I provide guidance,
support personalized for you.
Okay, this is way too small. This text
is hard to read.
If we look at the hierarchy here, why
is your name randomly in
the top corner bigger than the very thing
that you want here?
Okay, we need a promise as to what it
is I'm going to get.
Like do amazing handstands,
build calisthenics, become mobile.
Don't start with guidance, mate.
No one woke up today going, "God,
I wish I had
some guidance." So let's just make this
copy a little bit better.
Coaching options.
There's not a lot here, mate.
There's not a lot here.
So I would go promise, subheading.
I would love to see some before
and afters as a reason to believe. This
is Scott.
He started working with me six months ago.
He couldn't do this. Now he can do this.
The way that works
is each week you're going to get set this.
This is the reason to believe.
I also don't know how much it costs.
I don't understand why this
is on a different page
and not on the first page if I'm
completely honest. Now,
not the best looking page I've ever seen.
What is this hosted on?
I would say maybe use Leadpages
or something and
host something because I don't think this
is really doing you a service.
It's not bad,
but I would want all this information
here.
Or if this is the page
that you're sending me to,
all of these things I don't want
to have to click and do my homework.
You should be creating this for me.
What's this doing?
Way too many videos there.
You need to combine all of this
and put it into a landing page
that works because I
still don't really know what you do.
The guy before,
I know exactly what he does.
I was on his page fucking 30 seconds.
I knew exactly what he did.
Okay, this needs work.
Be a healthier being. Get healthy. Huh?
Okay, so that's above the fold.
I think that's a bit naff
if I'm honest because
look, if we go down, let's get healthy
and live a better life.
That to me is a much better above the
fold. Do you not agree?
So I would rather we land on this Than
that.
Because this is just kind of cut it.
Who's she? Don't know.
That stock image, she's got to go.
Get healthy, terrible call to action.
Let's get healthy and live a better life.
Subheading under that.
Let's have a look at what you say.
This needs some work.
My site creates a platform.
We could say something here like,
"Getting healthier is
easy. You just need to do it right.
The way it works is there
are four pillars:
nutrition, workouts, programs, and coffee.
Using these four,
I will objectively help improve your
health markers." Then we
could go down maybe a little bit further.
What are the metrics
that we're using for health?
Is it going to be BMI, C-reactive protein,
blood work, cholesterol,
lipids, blood pressure? What
are we using here? What...
Oh, this is Dave. When I met him, he
was this weight. He's now lost 15kg.
We've improved all of his health markers.
Being healthy is a subjective thing,
right?
So we need to bring some kind of
objectivity into it.
This is just too much.
It's like a short novel you've written
here.
And the thing is, right,
I'm here for my own interests being on
here.
And again,
you've tried to put all these things here.
It just needs to go onto one page,
because I'm going to land on here, and
the terminology is called bounce.
You think people are going to come here
and click all of these? They're not.
They're going to come and go, "Oh,
what's this? What's this?
No, don't really know what it is.
Bye." The Strength Guys.
Online powerlifting coaching. Okay,
you told me what it is.
Oh, for drug-free athletes. I like that.
You could call that natties or something,
but all right, drug-free athletes.
You've just said what it is.
I would love to like a promise.
Get stronger, lift more, perform better.
Through. Because this is the method.
This is what I'm getting.
This isn't the promise of the outcome
that's going to
come.
Because I'm here because I want to buy an
outcome.
I don't want to buy a method.
We need a VSL here because I'm on your
page.
I have no idea who the fuck you are,
what you look like.
If my friend goes, "Oh my God,
use The Strength Guys,"
and I come to a website and
I'm like, looks a bit robotic. Learn more.
No.
I'm not going to do that if I land here.
Work with us.
What our clients have to say. Again,
dark mode could work here.
This would be a perfect.
We need a heading.
What is the outcome I'm going to get?
A promise. Subheading. VSL.
Tell me about who you are, what you do,
who you help.
After three months of training, I
was able to press in full range of motion
with
bench presses for the first time in 10
years. Read the latest news.
I'm not mad on this one.
We need a lot more information.
Again,
have I got enough here to make an informed
decision?
And arguably, right,
if you've got six different things
that you're coaching here,
we do need six different landing pages.
So let's see if you've got a landing page
here. Mental skills coaching.
This page would work probably for someone
highly autistic, but I think we can do
better, especially at $125. The text
is just very
small. And some of you are like, "Oh,
but what about mobile?" Look, my wallet is
here. It's paid off my credit card.
I just bought a new lens for my camera,
going for a little 50 mil.
When I'm buying shit,
I do it at my desktop.
I do it here with my laptop
and computer and whatever.
So it's important
that you understand it's not just about
having incredible landing
pages,
it's about getting people at a time
that they're in the buying mentality.
So for instance, everything I buy
is here at home on my computer.
I pay off my credit cards,
all important stuff I do here.
When I pay Declan,
who's editing this video right now,
when he's getting
his fucking big payslip,
I don't do it on my phone when I'm out
and about.
I do it on my computer. This
is why we want to make sure we optimize
these for
desktops because people
are in mentality to buy.
Sat here, watching, creating.
In the links, send me your lead pages.
We can have a little look into them.
There's the free resources for you to jump
into. I can't help stress this enough.
Promise, subheading, VSL, call to action,
have some appeal to
authority, tell me what it is, what
is the outcome I get, give me
a reason to believe.
If you get those things,
people will land here, and they will
buy your shit. And even
if your conversion rate's one or 2%,
that's fine because to
double the amount of sales,
just send twice the amount of traffic.
And that can seem like a lot of work,
but over time,
as you get better at sending
traffic, it doesn't just move linear,
it moves like, whoa.
If you have any questions,
put them in below
and I'll answer them for you.
And then I'm going to go tidy the...
I'm not tidying this room.
Got to take the dog to the vet.
But anyway, you enjoy.
See you guys in a bit.
Bye-bye. Oh, there'll be a video here.
Watch that or don't. I'm not your dad.